Made in Ebisu
What? What? What?
Wait, wait, wait
No
Um
What is this?
Why? Why?
You always come on Saturdays
What?
You always come on Saturdays?
What do you mean?
I'm sorry
What did I say?
You cheated on me!
Anyway
I'm sorry
Wait, wait
Explain it to me
No
What is this?
Why did you come into my room?
I don't understand
Calm down
Is this your sister?
Yes
Come in
Seri
Where are you?
What are you doing?
I'm with my dad at Ginza
Wait
Come in
What's wrong?
I found a girl who looks like a student
But I don't want to have any more problems
Excuse me
She is the new girl, Seiran
Oh
No
Oh,
Super cute
Yes.
Right?
Isn't it a bit too much?
How about a shop?
No, it's not.
What if it's too much?
It's no good.
It's too much.
I'll help you with your graduation.
Sorry to interrupt you.
It's fine.
Give me a drink.
Yes, ma'am.
Something's wrong.
Don't ask me anything.
But I'll drink it.
I want to drink it.
Let me drink it.
With my dad's money.
Of course.
Don't underestimate me.
You're so loud.
You're so hardworking.
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
Cheers.
Something wonderful happened.
I was motivated to continue my studies.
I think it was the most wonderful day in my life.
It was the most wonderful day in my life.
That's right.
It was the worst day in my life.
No, no.
That's not it.
That's the best.
The best is the best.
I'm an idiot.
It was the worst day in my life.
I don't want to hear that.
Are you ready?
Are you ready to accept me?
No.
Are you going out?
You're not talking anymore.
That's right.
Dad.
I'm here.
You're a good man.
Thank you.
You gave me a lot of money.
I'm so happy.
I'm going to eat a bug from my nose.
Stop it.
I'm serious.
I'm going to be angry if I see you like this.
Seri.
You're cute.
Thank you.
Don't say that.
Are you laughing?
I'm a teacher.
I'm a human being.
I'm sorry.
Are you ready?
Take this and go with me.
I'd like to be by your side in the game.
I'm your fan.
I'm from Kisoku.
Excuse me, what can I do for you?
You're here because you have something to do, right?
Good morning.
Huh?
They're taking a break.
Is Sawaeya-san not here yet?
Okido-kun isn't here yet.
Amo-san and Isada-san aren't here yet.
Oh, nice timing.
Okido-kun, you're slightly late.
Sorry.
Long time no see.
Oh, right.
How's Yamazoi doing?
He's your teacher, right?
What? Did something happen to Yamazoi?
He's the worst.
What's with that old man?
He's a famous driver, Izumi-san.
He always tells us to stop when the typhoon is coming.
It happens every year.
Every year?
He's been quiet for the past few years.
I thought it was going to be hard.
It's not hard at all.
It's good to have a party.
But it's different from a festival.
Excuse me.
You're not going to have a big party, are you?
That's up to the teacher.
But if you want to compete,
you have to be excited.
Excited?
It's not like the people around you are bored.
It's like a hospital.
It's not like that.
But it's only once a year.
If it's only once a year, what can I do?
What can I do to be forgiven?
What are you talking about?
Excuse me.
I can't forgive you for anything.
But basically,
I want to make it clear to the neighbors.
It's not clear.
I'm giving up.
But I can't help it.
I can't say it even if I think it's bitter.
You know,
Silent Majority.
Your pronunciation is very good.
I learned it a lot as an English teacher.
I know.
I'm sure it's a former businessman who was sealed abroad.
What?
It's a milk shop.
I'm doing a milk delivery.
Can't you speak English with a milk delivery?
Do you have a complaint?
No, no.
It's not like that at all.
Excuse me.
Usually,
Otaku students don't listen to what I say.
Excuse me.
It's a streetcar.
A streetcar bicycle.
I told you not to ride a bicycle.
I won't stop running on the road.
It's a road that's decided by the school.
There are a lot of students ignoring it.
If you stop the bicycle in front of the store,
I told you it was a traffic jam.
I told you to stop the bicycle,
but you stopped it like a mountain.
Otaku students don't follow the rules.
That's right.
This is my point of view.
Education is to follow the rules.
School is to learn it.
It's a sports festival for that.
Sports have proper rules.
If you can't follow the rules,
there's no point in doing it.
That's why you should stop the sports festival.
What's wrong with that?
Stopping the sports festival?
Even so,
we can't stop the sports festival.
What?
Did you hear what I've been saying?
Don't make such a sad face.
That's enough.
Where's the principal?
Give me the principal.
It's hard to get excited from there.
The last one said,
it's because of the education.
It's because the direction of education is off.
That's right.
If you want to win the whole class,
go to the country.
How did you get the principal?
The board of education is late.
They're investigating the school.
It's only been four years.
They're destroying the family.
I'm sorry.
I can't forgive you.
I brought you some sweets.
You don't like sweets, do you?
This is a Dora-yaki from Hougetsu.
Who are you?
I'm Ishihara from the gym.
Yes.
Yes?
Is that why he stopped?
That's right.
Is that because Ishihara san was cute?
Is that why he stopped?
That, and the tea snack.
This is the basic manual for countermeasures.
Is there such a thing?
For older men,
treat beautiful young women.
For older women,
treat young and handsome women.
Really?
Mr. Yamazaki is a new student.
Do you know why he was arrested?
What?
Are you talking about protection?
Madam is weak against cute men.
Really?
That's complicated as an educator.
Lookism is scary.
That's the reality.
When you face a problem,
you can't solve it with just beautiful things.
That's what I think.
When you face a problem,
it's always related to humans.
Students, protectors, neighbors, residents,
and colleagues.
But that's why it should be right.
Isn't that right?
We are humans.
That's good.
It's hot as usual.
I'm shocked by how hot it is.
That's right.
Really?
So, be careful if you're using a bicycle.
But,
isn't it strange that you're being careful
because your father told you?
No, it's not like that.
It's because you're in trouble.
But,
what should we do when we go to Dagashia?
Dagashia?
Dagashia Jun.
Bonja Ekiya.
Shut up, Yamazai.
He's a teacher.
So,
what should we do when we stop in front of the store?
Shouldn't we go?
We're hungry after club activities.
We should go home and eat.
That's the tradition of the soccer club.
Go there after club activities and eat.
What kind of tradition is that?
But,
if you're in the way of traffic,
it's not good.
So, we shouldn't go?
We should leave the bicycle at the school.
It's a little far.
It's the soccer club, so let's run.
I see.
We're all the same.
Bonja Ekiya, don't go.
Okay.
If we don't go,
you'll take responsibility.
You can't say that.
Anyway,
if we leave the bicycle in front of the school,
it's not good.
It's a rule.
Besides,
I don't want you to talk about the rules.
Why?
It doesn't matter.
You've been riding with two people lately.
Is that so?
No, it's just a coincidence.
It's not a coincidence.
You're with Yamamoto near your house.
What?
You can't ride with two people.
Why are you with Yamamoto?
Don't you know?
I've been with Yamamoto since last week.
It's hot.
Congratulations.
Shut up.
It's not hot.
It's hot.
And
I think he's talking about the three-way meeting,
but
about Shindo.
That's all.
Two jobs.
Stand up.
Shohei,
you're not the one today. It's me.
Stand up.
Please.
Be careful.
Bow
Good morning.
Okido, can I talk to you?
Sawaiya, can I talk to you?
Yes.
The three-way meeting hasn't started yet.
Do you want to talk to your parents?
I don't think they'll come to school.
I'd like to talk to them.
My father is busy with work.
Bye.
I don't think they'll come either.
I see.
You were late today, right?
I'm sorry.
Call me when you're off or late.
I'll be careful from now on.
Tell me if you need anything.
Yeah.
I'll be right there.
Is it possible that Sawaiya and Minamida...
No.
Kengo seems to be popular, but he's not dating anyone.
By the way,
can I meet Sawaiya and Okido at the three-way meeting?
That's right.
Are you going to meet Okido at the three-way meeting?
Yes, I'm going to meet Sawaiya.
I'm going to the three-way meeting because I'm busy.
Okido has a single father, right?
Oh, that's right.
Sawaiya has a single mother.
I've never heard of it.
What is it?
Whose?
It's a food business.
Oh, that's right.
There's a rumor that Okido's father is a violent man.
It's a rumor, so it's a rumor.
Are you going?
I see.
That's it.
Teachers don't have to deal with anyone.
My stomach hurts.
Kengo.
My name is Masa.
I've liked you for a while.
Can you go out with me?
I'm sorry.
I didn't think about it.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
Are you okay?
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
I'm Seira.
Oh, Seira.
Yes, yes, yes.
Thank you very much.
How's the after party today?
I didn't do the after party.
We talked about it last time.
Are you serious?
Yes.
It's far away.
It's not that far away.
Really?
Can I have it?
Go ahead.
Hello.
Welcome.
You finally brought the guests.
Nice to meet you.
It's nice.
It's like a snack for the bus.
Are you praising the bus?
Are you a student?
I'm praising it.
Thank you.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Natsuko.
Mom.
You're my mom.
I'm your mom.
Please sit down.
You're beautiful.
You look like your daughter.
No.
She looks like me.
I'll have this.
Please enjoy it.
Are you going home?
It's a little later.
You're early tomorrow.
My real name is Lena.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
I'll call you Lena from now on.
I'm used to being friends with my mom.
Let's drink a little more.
Lena.
Mr. Yoshida.
You're so erotic.
It's dangerous.
Are you walking properly?
I'm walking.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Yu.
What's going on?
I'm home.
You're serious.
Stop it.
Yu.
I'm home.
A party game?
Are you studying properly?
Stop it.
I'm not studying without a joke.
You don't have money to go to high school anyway.
That's because I have a scholarship.
It's okay.
I don't have money to go to high school.
You don't have to worry.
I don't want to study because I work.
Imagine.
It's raining and you can't do anything.
You're waiting for the rain to stop.
The sun is setting.
From 5 o'clock on Monday afternoon next week.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
What are you doing?
You brought me a lot of presents.
Squid.
Squid ink paste.
It's your mother's birthday soon.
It's my mother's birthday.
You're going abroad next month, right?
I'll be in Boston for about a month.
You didn't know?
You're going to Harvard?
It's a different company.
If you quit your job now, you'll have a hard time.
You have to do this.
You're wrong as a lover.
This is it.
You bought me chocolate brownies.
You're my favorite.
I'll be right back.
Where's the rice?
I don't need it.
I'll eat it later.
Hurry up.
Excuse me.
Isn't this crazy?
What do you mean?
I'm a big fan of you.
Of course.
What are you going to do now?
I'm going to...
I'm going to break up with you.
What?
Is this the end of us?
You know...
I'm so sorry.
I betrayed you.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what you're saying.
You know...
You didn't cheat on me.
What?
You dated her, didn't you?
No.
You didn't cheat on me.
I saw his reaction.
What?
Who is it?
It's cold.
Why?
You always come on Saturdays.
I was with you on Saturdays.
You always come on Saturdays?
What do you mean?
Who is that person?
Why does she come on Saturdays?
You mean I cheated on you?
No.
That's not true.
What do you mean?
You dated her, didn't you?
That's...
I'm so sorry.
Don't say sorry. Since when?
When did you start dating her?
When? Are you listening?
About a year ago.
Hey, hey, hey.
I'm just kidding.
What do you mean?
I don't know what you mean.
You're so annoying.
I'm sorry.
But we broke up.
I don't care if we broke up.
Don't go out with me.
What are you going to do about the wedding?
I don't know what to do.
I was betrayed.
I'm sure I'm going to get hurt.
Wait a minute.
The eyes of the world and the voice are irrelevant.
If you get over it,
it's better for you to be happy.
I can't believe it.
It's not like that.
What are you talking about?
You want me to tell you about what happened last night, don't you?
You're not stupid.
I see.
It's just my story.
What are you talking about?
It's like I have a reason.
Then listen.
What?
We were dating.
We weren't dating?
We said we were going to see each other once every two or three weeks.
We were just coming over.
We were just hanging out.
We talked on the phone.
We talked once a week.
We talked about the message.
We talked about waking up every day.
We were so busy.
We said we'd live together.
We said we couldn't.
My parents wouldn't let me do that.
Your parents?
You know...
How important was I to you?
What?
It was important.
How important was I to you?
What percent?
You're doing a great job.
I've always respected you.
You always said you were good at talking to your classmates.
But...
You've never been so serious about me since you started being so serious about me.
That's not true.
I just started being serious.
I wanted you to stop.
I told you I was going to stop.
I won't stop.
I told you I was going to tell you.
It was because of that.
You're not going to stop?
At least...
Until the students who took the class...
Then Rio...
Then Rio won't change.
Rio's life is...
What is that?
It's like I'm the only one who's bad.
That's not true.
Then can I make up for it?
Then can I make another woman?
I'm sorry.
That's the worst.
But it's strange.
I don't want to live as a human being.
If you want to be a teacher,
If you are serious about being a teacher,
How can I know what kind of couple we are?
Don't say that to me!
Even I...
I'm sorry.
I'm so tired.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm sorry.
Rio.
Don't come to my house.
I'm serious.
I understand.
Rio.
I'll call you again.
The next day
If you're excited about the Golden Week,
It's a midterm test.
Don't just play during the break.
Got it?
Right?
For the job hunting group,
Especially the midterm and final exams of the first semester
The results will be decided.
That's all.
Let's go.
Bow.
Bye.
Rio.
Tomorrow?
Tomorrow.
You can go now.
You can go tomorrow.
Hey, Rio.
What's wrong?
Do you have a boyfriend?
What?
What's going on?
It's not like that.
Everyone's interested in him.
Especially the boys.
Rio has a boyfriend.
Right.
What do you think?
He definitely has one.
That's right.
Rio is so cute.
So cute.
Did he go to high school?
No, he didn't.
He was studying.
He was single?
Yes.
What about college?
He was a student, right?
Well, well, well.
Me?
Well, I'm a picky person.
So I have a lot of stupid things.
Well, well, well.
What about your boyfriend in college?
Did he have one?
Yes, he did.
Well, well, well.
Wait, wait, wait.
How do you know each other?
Do you know each other?
We have the same circle.
Wow.
You look like a circle.
Did you date anyone during college?
Only one.
One?
That's amazing.
Wow.
I'm so jealous.
That's amazing.
By the way,
are you dating him now?
What?
Wait, wait, wait.
I want to see him.
Ms. Sasaoka.
Long time no see.
I've been waiting for your invitation.
Can you come out soon?
No, no, no.
Well,
After the exhibition.
Well, I'll go ahead.
See you later.
Well, thank you for your hard work.
Mr. Okuma.
Wait, hey.
Well, Mr. Okuma.
He's still young.
No.
He has a strong mentality.
It's not a mental problem.
That's our right.
It's our right.
It's better to go home to the exhibition.
But that's a building.
No, no, no.
Please.
Oh, no, it's okay.
Is that okay?
Yeah, it's okay.
Don't worry.
My hand is...
I'm sorry.
It's deep.
Thank you for waiting.
Buffalo wings.
Cheers.
By the way,
did Ms. Kaito have a girlfriend?
I didn't know you were talking about that.
No.
I'm looking for a wife.
What?
What about you two?
I don't have one.
I have a second wife.
What?
Mr. Goh,
you have a second wife at that young age?
Yeah.
What about your children?
No, I don't.
What about your girlfriend?
Well, well.
Well, I guess so.
And Mr. Goh seems to be free and popular.
Mr. Kaito doesn't seem to be popular.
He's handsome.
Naos is very rude, but he's not rude.
Don't you want a girlfriend?
I want one.
Of course I want one.
That's a bad way to work.
What?
Mr. Kaito's way of working is very bad.
The world is small,
and he only has students and protectors.
Isn't that bad?
It's bad as a teacher.
It's bad.
But that's the reality.
If you go back in time,
your life will open up in that sense.
You're right.
Mr. Sasaoka had a boyfriend, didn't he?
Idiot.
What?
That's what I'm talking about.
Recently,
there's been a lot going on.
Oh.
A lot going on?
Idiot.
What?
Well,
school is the cradle of love,
so it's hard to find a link.
You think so?
Yes.
It's the same as before.
If I hadn't had a relationship with him,
it wouldn't have happened.
Did you break up with him?
He cheated on me.
What?
In fact,
he made me laugh
because he thought I was cheating on him.
In such a messy classroom life,
a major heart attack
broke out.
When I actually broke up with him,
like a divorce,
or my parents' death,
I wondered
how the teachers
got over it.
It's a family problem.
When a major heart attack broke out in private,
how did the teachers get over it?
Well,
I didn't ask Mr. Kaito.
Right.
How did Mr. Go get over it?
Well,
I...
the more I think about school,
the more I think about us.
Recently,
we started dating in our class.
We told each other,
don't ride bikes.
We were careful.
Well,
I remember
the university days.
We were scolded
for doing the same thing.
As my students do,
we walked around the campus together.
When our classmates
were having fun in love,
we would flashback
When I was in college,
we were in the same circle.
And
at first,
I was the one who confessed to him.
But he rejected me.
I really loved him.
I admired him.
I attacked him several times.
And I started dating him.
It's strange.
Where?
Where did he take me?
I loved him so much.
I was proud of him.
He told me everything.
He laughed at me.
When I got home,
he bought me my favorite chocolate brownie
and waited for me.
The other day,
the other day,
he gave me a ring.
He said he wanted to marry me.
Open it.
He was the first one I dated.
He was the only one I dated.
So,
I was the happiest woman in the world.
No matter how hard it is for me,
I can overcome it.
It's strange.
Why?
Why did he take me?
I should have done it.
Mr. Goh.
It's hard.
Pretending to be normal in front of the students.
It's really hard.
When I'm having a hard time,
come with me.
Excuse me.
Can I talk to you?
I'm a human being.
Wake up, mom.
I'm going home.
I'm sorry. It's over.
Please subscribe to my favorite MyList channel.
If you want to enjoy the previous episodes,
please watch it on Younext and Netflix.
Kengo.
I've liked you for a long time.
Will you go out with me?
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?